{
    "subject": "resource/Gene_Hackman",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/San_Bernardino,_California",
    "human_readable": "Gene Hackman was born in San Bernardino, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8750445246696472,
            "question": "Is Gene Hackman from California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612608909606934,
            "question": "Where was Gene Hackman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8458932042121887,
            "question": "What city in California is associated with Gene Hackman's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308461308479309,
            "question": "What state was Gene Hackman born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474292516708374,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Gene Hackman was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7052289247512817,
            "question": "What US state was Gene Hackman born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6158706545829773,
            "question": "Where did Gene Hackman originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5396170616149902,
            "question": "Can you tell me Gene Hackman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5261052250862122,
            "question": "In which city did Gene Hackman begin his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.51606684923172,
            "question": "San Bernardino, California, is known as the birthplace of which actor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gene Hackman was born in San Bernardino, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city did Gene Hackman begin his life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Gene Hackman's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Gene Hackman originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8692_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information from the documents supports that Gene Hackman was indeed born in San Bernardino, California. Multiple documents mention his birthplace as San Bernardino, California, on January 30, 1930."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}